<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Arknights Guide</string>

    <string name="heroes_name">Nama Pahlawan</string>
    <string name="description">Deskripsi</string>
    <string name="desc_app">Deskripsi Aplikasi</string>
    <string name="nama">Ikhlasul Amal Rivel</string>
    <string name="email">amalrivel@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="bio">Semangat</string>
    <string name="link_github">https://github.com/amalrivel</string>
    <string-array name="data_name">
        <item>Cantabile</item>
        <item>Minimalist</item>
        <item>Pozëmka</item>
        <item>Gavial the Invincible</item>
        <item>Ebenholz</item>
        <item>Hibiscus the Purifier</item>
        <item>Czerny</item>
        <item>Erato</item>
        <item>Windflit</item>
        <item>Lumen</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="data_description">
        <item>A woman who grew up in the midst of disorder, with hopes of seeking a new direction here.</item>
        <item>Durin architectural designer Minimalist, hauled surface-side by Gavial.</item>
        <item>Sniper Operator Pozëmka, the one who cherished Zeruertza most of all Zeruertzans.</item>
        <item>The Gavial you know and love. (Toting a battleaxe.)</item>
        <item>Caster Operator Ebenholz refuses to add any unnecessary prefixes in front of his name.</item>
        <item>Hibiscus the Purifier, Rhodes Island Medical Operator; her ideal of caring for the sick and wounded has never wavered.</item>
        <item>Czerny, musician from the Afterglow, journeying with the rhythm.</item>
        <item>A wandering bard from Minos, ready to explore the unknown scenery with you.</item>
        <item>A fresh college graduate from Columbia—he\'s finally found a company that\'ll give him a job offer.</item>
        <item>Lumen, chapel caregiver of Gran Faro, here to soothe your wounds.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="data_archetype">
        <item>Agent</item>
        <item>Drone / Mech-Accord</item>
        <item>Close Range / Heavyshooter</item>
        <item>AoE / Centurion</item>
        <item>Charge / Mystic Caster</item>
        <item>Incantation</item>
        <item>Arts Protector</item>
        <item>Heavyweight / Besieger</item>
        <item>Artificer</item>
        <item>Wide-Range / Therapist</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="data_traits">
        <item>Has reduced Redeployment Time, can use ranged attacks</item>
        <item>Controls a Drone to deal Arts damage to an enemy; When the Drone continuously attacks the same enemy, its damage will increase (up to 110% of the operators ATK)</item>
        <item>High accuracy point-blank shot</item>
        <item>Attacks all blocked enemies [This in-game description is inaccurate. This Operator does not need enemies to be blocked to hit them, they just need to be in range. This Operator hits multiple targets equal to their block number.]</item>
        <item>Attacks deal Arts damage; When unable to find a target, attacks can be stored up and fired all at once (Up to 3 charges)</item>
        <item>Attacks deal Arts damage and heal the HP of an ally within Attack Range for 50% of the damage dealt</item>
        <item>Normal attacks deal Arts damage while the skill is active</item>
        <item>Attacks the heaviest enemy first</item>
        <item>Blocks 2 enemies; Can use Support Devices in battles</item>
        <item>Has a large healing range, but the healing amount on farther targets is reduced to {heal_scale:0%}</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="data_operator_overview">
        <item>A great unit that can fill many roles well for a small roster. She can generate good DP while also contributing decent damage, which is especially useful in early game. She stays relevant into end game, which means her 5 star development costs aren\'t wasted.</item>
        <item>A consistent-damage oriented caster that won\'t perform well enough to justify the higher costs compared to lower rarity counterparts. New players should spend resources elsewhere.</item>
        <item>A strong DPS unit with versatility that can keep herself safe (or make up for poor positioning) with her deployables. On the flip side, managing and redeploying her summon may add an undesirable layer of complexity for some players still learning the game.</item>
        <item>A great starter 6 star for a new roster. She provides blocking, damage, and bulk, along with a self sustain option, which offerst the power and flexibility to help players roll the early game. She\'s a strong contributor at E1, enabling players to invest in higher-improvement early E2\'s.</item>
        <item>His targetting and range peculiarities along with the complexity of the kit and the relatively high amount of micromanagement required to maximize his performance are not ideal for new players learning the game. Most new players will be better off spending the resources elsewhere.</item>
        <item>Hybrid roles can be useful to new players with limited rosters, and in the early game when healing requirements aren\'t particularly high, the damage/healing combo can make pushing through stages easier/quicker if players don\'t already have stronger hybrid or dps options. That being said, players will typically be better off developing their strong specialized roleplayers, and the healing/range restrictions can be troublesome for players still learning the game.</item>
        <item>Blockers that can also deal good damage, and melee sources of Arts damage can be quite useful in the early game for limited rosters, but this archetype quickly becomes outclassed in more difficult content. The 5 Star development cost is too high here for what it contributes to the roster.</item>
        <item>Sleep tends to be an awkward crowd control option even for advanced players because of the drawback of most Operators not being able to attack Sleeping enemies. For new players, the drawbacks and additional planning/awareness that is required won\'t be worth the potential benefits most of the time.</item>
        <item>Doesn\'t dps very well, doesn\'t support very well, and is a pain-in-the-ass to use even for experienced players. All at an expensive 5 Star development cost. New players should avoid wasting limited rescources here.</item>
        <item>Lumen is a 6★ Medic [Wide Range / Therapist] that specializes in the immediate removal of negative status effects!</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="data_reference">
        <item>https://gamepress.gg/arknights/operator/cantabile</item>
        <item>https://gamepress.gg/arknights/operator/minimalist</item>
        <item>https://gamepress.gg/arknights/operator/pozemka</item>
        <item>https://gamepress.gg/arknights/operator/gavial-invincible</item>
        <item>https://gamepress.gg/arknights/operator/ebenholz</item>
        <item>https://gamepress.gg/arknights/operator/hibiscus-purifier</item>
        <item>https://gamepress.gg/arknights/operator/czerny</item>
        <item>https://gamepress.gg/arknights/operator/erato</item>
        <item>https://gamepress.gg/arknights/operator/windflit</item>
        <item>https://gamepress.gg/arknights/operator/lumen</item>
    </string-array>
    <integer-array name="data_photo">
        <item>@drawable/cantabile</item>
        <item>@drawable/minimalist</item>
        <item>@drawable/pozemka</item>
        <item>@drawable/gavial</item>
        <item>@drawable/ebenholz</item>
        <item>@drawable/hibiscus</item>
        <item>@drawable/czerny</item>
        <item>@drawable/erato</item>
        <item>@drawable/windflit</item>
        <item>@drawable/lumen</item>
    </integer-array>
    <integer-array name="data_photo_faction">
        <item>@drawable/rhodes</item>
        <item>@drawable/sargon</item>
        <item>@drawable/rhodes</item>
        <item>@drawable/rhodes</item>
        <item>@drawable/leithanien</item>
        <item>@drawable/rhodes</item>
        <item>@drawable/leithanien</item>
        <item>@drawable/minos</item>
        <item>@drawable/columbia</item>
        <item>@drawable/iberia</item>
    </integer-array>
    <integer-array name="data_full_photo">
        <item>@drawable/fcantabile</item>
        <item>@drawable/fminimalist</item>
        <item>@drawable/fpozemka</item>
        <item>@drawable/fgavial</item>
        <item>@drawable/febenholz</item>
        <item>@drawable/fhibiscus</item>
        <item>@drawable/fczerny</item>
        <item>@drawable/ferato</item>
        <item>@drawable/fwindflit</item>
        <item>@drawable/flumen</item>
    </integer-array>
    <integer-array name="data_photo_class">
        <item>@drawable/class_vanguard</item>
        <item>@drawable/class_caster</item>
        <item>@drawable/class_sniper</item>
        <item>@drawable/class_guard</item>
        <item>@drawable/class_caster</item>
        <item>@drawable/class_medic</item>
        <item>@drawable/class_tank</item>
        <item>@drawable/class_sniper</item>
        <item>@drawable/class_support</item>
        <item>@drawable/class_medic</item>
    </integer-array>
</resources>